Julius W. Becton Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Oversize, 1969-1994 (Box OV 1-OV 11)
  - Army Career (Box OV 1)
    - Newspapers and newspaper clippings, Austin American-Statesman, "1st Cavalry Division honors last horse troopers, Boots and Saddles at Fort Hood," enlarged feature article, 1975 (Container 10) (Box OV 1)
    - Troop review, 1st Cavalry, photograph, 1975 (Container 11) (Box OV 1)
    - 7th Corps, scrapbooks, 1978-1981 (Container 25), (3 folders) (Box OV 2-4)
    - 101st Airbourne Division, 17th Regiment, Post-retirement, honorary colonel, scrapbook, 1988 (Container 32) (Box OV 5)
    - Training and Doctrine Command, Becton reviewing Air Force troops, Lackland Air Force Base, San Antonio, Tex., photograph, 1982 (Container 65) (Box OV 5)
  - Federal Emergency Management Agency (Box OV 6)
    - "The FEMA Story," scrapbook, undated (Container 86) (Box OV 6)
    - Federation of World Volunteer Firefighters Associations, honors awarded to Becton, 1986 (Container 83) (Box OV 7)
    - Forest Service, award, 1987 (Box OV 7)
    - Speeches, 1987, Aberdeen Proving Ground, Maryland, photo thank you card, 1987 (Container 92) (Box OV 1)
  - Prairie View A & M University, Prairie View, Tex. (Box OV 8)
    - Historically black colleges and universities, National Association for Equal Opportunity in Higher Education, 1988 (Container 105) (Box OV)
    - Retirement, "A Book of Memories," scrapbook, retirement from Prairie View, 1994 (Container 122) (Box OV 8)
    - Speeches, poster, 1990 (Container 122) (Box OV 1)
  - Organizations (Box OV 8)
    - American Battle Monuments Commission, The National World War II Memorial 2004 Calendar, 2004 (Container 150) (Box OV 8)
    - Dwight D. Eisenhower Society, certificate of charter membership, 1986 (Container 156) (Box OV 1)
  - Subject File (Box OV 9)
    - African American military history, Golden Buffalo Presents Black Military History, 1770-1975, calendar, 1989-1990 (Container 191) (Box OV 9)
  - Family papers (Box OV 8)
    - Glasco, G., Becton's son-in-law, group photograph with members of his class of student helicopter pilots, 1969 (Container 193) (Box OV 10)
  - Miscellany (Box OV 10)
    - Photograph, color portrait of Becton, undated (Container 197) (Box OV 10)
    - Bluford, Guion Stewart, astronaut, color photographic portrait, undated (Container 197) (Box OV 10)
  - Cartoons and caricatures, undated (Container 197) (Box OV 11)